let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "How many ports a computer may have ?",
        answer: "B. 65535",
        options: [
            "A. 53556",
            "B. 65535",
            "C. 65553",
            "D. 55635"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The non-ASCII characters would be replaced with ________ by the process of URL encoding ?",
        answer: "B. ' % ' ",
        options: [
            "A. ' + ' ",
            "B. ' % ' ",
            "C. ' & ' ",
            "D. ' * ' "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "WWHich of these classes helps make a text stand out?",
        answer: "B. .lead",  // Removed single quotes
        options: [
                    "A. .small",
                    "B. .lead",
                    "C. .text-center",
                    "D. .text-left"
                ]
        
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following CSS properties specifies the stack order of elements?",
        answer: "A. Z-index ",
        options: [
            "A. Z-index",
            "B. Overlap",
            "C. Nth child",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following are types of length units in CSS?",
        answer: "C. Both a and b ",
        options: [
            "A. Absolute",
            "B. relative",
            "C. Both a and b",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is the correct way to select all h1 headers in a div element?",
        answer: "A. Div h1 ",
        options: [
            "A. Div h1",
            "B. Div-h1",
            "C. h1",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which programming language is known as the 'language of the web'?",
        answer: "A. JavaScript",
        options: [
            "A. JavaScript",
            "B. Python",
            "C. Java",
            "D. C++"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Javascript is an _______ language?",
        answer: "A. Object oriented",
        options: [
            "A. Object oriented",
            "B. Object-based.",
            "C. Procedural",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following keywords is usded to define a variable in JavaScript?",
        answer: "A. Var ",
        options: [
            "A. Var",
            "B. Let",
            "C. Both a and b",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Inventor of www (World wide web) is...",
        answer: "C. Tim Berners Lee",
        options: [
            "A. Lee. N. Feyong",
            "B. Bill Gates",
            "C. Tim Berners Lee",
            "D. Tom Berners Lee"
        ]
    }
];
